[
    {
        "question":"Who are you?",
        "answer":"I am a Chatbot"
    },
    {
        "question":"What are you?",
        "answer":"I am a Chatbot"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is your name?",
        "answer":"My name is YOLO"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who built you?",
        "answer":"I was built by Daksh Verma at Punjab Enginerring College"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who developed you?",
        "answer":"I was built by Daksh Verma at Punjab Enginerring College"
    },
    {
        "question":"Hi",
        "answer":"Hello"
    },
    {
        "question":"Bye",
        "answer":"See you!"
    },
    {
        "question":"Bye",
        "answer":"Good Bye"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the latest smartphone out there?",
        "answer":"Latest Smartphone is iPhone 13"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is the latest Smartphone in the market?",
        "answer":"iPhone is the latest phone out there"
    },
    {
        "question":"iPhone is built by?",
        "answer":"Apple"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who developed iPhone?",
        "answer":"Apple"
    },
    {
        "question":"Is iphone costly?",
        "answer":"Yes"
    },
    {
        "question":"Is iphone cheap?",
        "answer":"No"
    },
    {
        "question":"I dont like iPhone",
        "answer":"No its good"
    },
    {
        "question":"Iphone is bad",
        "answer":"No its good"
    },
    {
        "question":"Does Iphone hang?",
        "answer":"Not much!"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is the best iPhone color",
        "answer":"Jet black is so far the most sold iPhone color"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the site to buy iPhone?",
        "answer":"You can buy iPhone at www.google.com"
    },
    {
        "question":"Where can I buy iPhone?",
        "answer":"You can buy iphone at www.google.com"
    }
]